A Guide to the JDR 3rd Fund records FA081
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Arts in Education Program - Kathryn Bloom Files, 1967-1979; 11; 88 Cubic Feet 204 document cases
  - Arts in Education Program - Kathryn Bloom Files - Project Files, 11.B
    - Ridge Street School - Miscellany - Planning Conference, January 14, 1970 (Box 224, Folder 1643)
    - Ridgewood Public Schools - Project File, 1971-1975 (Box 224, Folder 1644)
      Grant #B-7374-E, #B-73108-E
    - Ridgewood Public Schools - Reports, 1973 (Box 224, Folder 1645)
    - Ridgewood Public Schools - Meetings, 1972-1973 (Box 225, Folder 1646)
    - Ridgewood Public Schools - Brochures, 1972-1977 (Box 225, Folder 1647)
    - Ridgewood Public Schools - Circulating Art Collection, 1976 (Box 225, Folder 1648)
    - Ridgewood Public Schools - Handbook - Art-Humanities Department, 1973 (Box 225, Folder 1649)
    - Ridgewood Public Schools - Search Sheets for Museums and Heritage Studies (Box 225, Folder 1650)
    - Ridgewood Public Schools - Related Projects - North Adams, 1973-1974 (Box 225, Folder 1651)
    - Ridgewood Public Schools - Related Projects - Project Discovery, 1967 (Box 226, Folder 1652)
    - Ridgewood Public Schools - Related Projects - Project PACE (Performing Arts Curriculum Enrichment), 1967-1974 (Box 226, Folder 1653)
    - Ridgewood Public Schools - Related Projects - Project TAP (Television Arts Project), 1973 (Box 226, Folder 1654)
    - Ridgewood Public Schools - Related Projects - Project Zero, 1968-1971 (Box 226, Folder 1655)
    - Ridgewood Public Schools - Responses to Letter of January 16, 1975 (Box 226, Folder 1656)
    - University City Public Schools - Project File, 1967-1970 (Box 226, Folder 1657)
      Grant #B-6866-E, #B-7087-E, #B-71112-E
    - University City Public Schools - Project File, 1967-1970 (Box 226, Folder 1658)
    - University City Public Schools - Project File, 1971-1977 (Box 227, Folder 1659)
    - University City Public Schools - Project File, 1971-1977 (Box 227, Folder 1660)
    - University City Public Schools - Project Profile (Box 227, Folder 1661)
    - University City Public Schools - Reports - Summary of Progress Reports, May 1968-July 1971 (Box 227, Folder 1662)
    - University City Public Schools - Reports, Progress, May 1968-October 1973 (Box 227, Folder 1663)
    - University City Public Schools - Reports, Progress, May 1968-October 1973 (Box 227, Folder 1664)
    - University City Public Schools - Meetings, 1968-1974 (Box 228, Folder 1665)
    - University City Public Schools - "All the Arts for Every Child" - Copy of Publication, 1973 (Box 228, Folder 1666)
    - University City Public Schools - "All the Arts for Every Child" - Final Draft (Box 228, Folder 1667)
    - University City Public Schools - "All the Arts for Every Child" - Contract File, 1973-1976 (Box 228, Folder 1668)
    - University City Public Schools - "All the Arts for Every Child" - Correspondence, 1971-1976 (Box 228, Folder 1669)
    - University City Public Schools - "All the Arts for Every Child" - Press Conference, January 30, 1973 (Box 228, Folder 1670)
    - University City Public Schools - "All the Arts for Every Child" - Clippings, 1973-1974 (Box 228, Folder 1671)
    - University City Public Schools - "All the Arts for Every Child" - Brochures and Clippings, 1968-1975 (Box 228, Folder 1672)
    - University City Public Schools - Miscellany - "Activities for Greater Awareness", 1972 (Box 229, Folder 1673)
    - University City Public Schools - Miscellany - "Arts in General Education" - Packets, 1968 (Box 229, Folder 1674)
    - University City Public Schools - Miscellany - "Arts in General Education" - Packets, 1968 (Box 229, Folder 1675)
    - University City Public Schools - Miscellany - "Arts in General Education" - Workshop, June 16-17, 1968 (Box 229, Folder 1676)
    - University City Public Schools - Miscellany - "Arts in General Education" - Workshop, June 16-17, 1968 (Box 229, Folder 1677)
    - University City Public Schools - Miscellany (C) (Box 229, Folder 1678)
    - University City Public Schools - Miscellany (E-H) (Box 229, Folder 1679)
    - University City Public Schools - Miscellany - Metropolitan Educational Center of the Arts, 1968-1969 (Box 230, Folder 1680)
    - University City Public Schools - Miscellany (P-So) (Box 230, Folder 1681)
    - University City Public Schools - Miscellany (Sp-V) (Box 230, Folder 1682)
    - Declinations (A-Am) (Box 230, Folder 1683)
    - Declinations (An-Az) (Box 230, Folder 1684)
    - Declinations (Ba-Be) (Box 231, Folder 1685)
    - Declinations (Bl-Bz) (Box 231, Folder 1686)
    - Declinations (Ca) (Box 231, Folder 1687)
    - Declinations (Ce) (Box 231, Folder 1688)
    - Declinations (Ci-Co) (Box 231, Folder 1689)
    - Declinations (Cr-Cz) (Box 232, Folder 1690)
    - Declinations (D-E) (Box 232, Folder 1691)
    - Declinations (F) (Box 232, Folder 1692)
    - Declinations (G-H) (Box 232, Folder 1693)
    - Declinations (I) (Box 232, Folder 1694)
    - Declinations (J-L) (Box 233, Folder 1695)
    - Declinations (Ma-Me) (Box 233, Folder 1696)
    - Declinations (Mi-Mz) (Box 233, Folder 1697)
    - Declinations (Na-New J) (Box 233, Folder 1698)
    - Declinations (New M-Nz) (Box 233, Folder 1699)
    - Declinations (O) (Box 234, Folder 1700)
    - Declinations (Pa-Pe) (Box 234, Folder 1701)
    - Declinations (Ph-Pz) (Box 234, Folder 1702)
    - Declinations (Q-Ri) (Box 234, Folder 1703)
    - Declinations (Ro-Rz) (Box 234, Folder 1704)
    - Declinations (Sa) (Box 235, Folder 1705)
    - Declinations (Sc-Sp) (Box 235, Folder 1706)
    - Declinations (St-Sz) (Box 235, Folder 1707)
    - Declinations (Ta-Th) (Box 235, Folder 1708)
    - Declinations (To-Uz) (Box 235, Folder 1709)
    - Declinations (Va-Vi) (Box 236, Folder 1710)
    - Declinations (Vo-We) (Box 236, Folder 1711)
    - Declinations (Wh-Z) (Box 236, Folder 1712)
    - Declinations Destroyed - List, 1968-1971 (Box 236, Folder 1713)
    - Curriculum Tools - IMPACT: Commentary for Arts Slides, Slide Carousel, and Cassette with Script (Box CT 1, Folder 1)
    - Curriculum Tools - "Integrating the Arts" (Prabha Sabasrabudhe for Mineola Public Schools, 1973) (Box CT 2, Folder 1)
      Activity file cards and Handbook.
    - Curriculum Tools - "Theatre Game File" (Brian Hansen and Judie Contrucci for Central Midwestern Regional Educational Laboratory, Inc. (CEMREL), 1971) (Box CT 3, Folder 1)
    - Slides - Baldwin School of Puerto Rico - Slides Accompanying Report, June 10, 1973; 10 slides; photographs (Box S 1, Folder 3)
      See also Box 151, Folder 1181
    - Slides - Project IMPACT, n.d.; 28 slides; photographs (Box S 1, Folder 4)
      See also Box 178, Folder 1360, through Box 184, Folder 1406
    - Slides - Jefferson County Schools - Slides Accompanying Report by J. Chen, 1974; 15 slides; photographs (Box S 1, Folder 5)
      See also Box 187, Folders 1421-1423
    - Slides - John Adams High School - Slides Accompanying Report, January 1974; 40 slides; photographs (Box S 2, Folder 6)
      See also Box 189, Folders 1434-1435
    - Slides - PS 3-M - Slides Accompanying Report by E. Wiener for 1972-73, 126 slides; photographs (Box S 2, Folder 7)
      REPORT ON THE ARTS AT P.S. 3 - E. Wiener 1. Photograms. 2.-6. Graphics. (Slides 5.-8. by Suzanne Dahlquist.) 7. Working with the printing press. 8. Weaving. 9. Hall painting. 10.-13. Woodshop, fourth floor. 14.-15. Tie-dyed reading nook, fourth floor. 16. Art room, fourth floor. 17.-19. Needlepoint workshop. 20.-21. Painted study cubicles, hall. 22. Hall painting. 23. Mobile. 24.-25. Geodesic structures (straws). 26.-27. Ecological environment, fourth floor.
      Kathy Lewis' Class (Slides 28-61): 28.-31. Calendar. 32.-33. Window decorations. 34.-36. "Eating Game." 37. Drawing. 38. Magic Marker drawing. 39. Drawing. 40. Detail of no. 39. 41.-52. Folded paper dyeing. 53.-54. Drip dyeing. 55.-61. Anti-war posters.
      62.-72. "Shapes" 74. -100. Al Loving Event. 101.-110. Bill Taggert Event. 111.-119. Ivan Film, tie-dyeing sessions. (Slides by S. Dahlquist.) 120.-125. Graphics Fair. 126. Room on the fifth floor.
  - Arts in Education Program - Kathryn Bloom Files - Contact File, 11.C
    This subseries consists of correspondence, reports, memoranda, records of meetings, brochures, and publications relating to contacts between the Arts in Education Program and agencies on all levels of government, arts and educational organizations and institutions, foundations, museums, and other institutions.
    - United States Government Agencies - Alliance for Arts Education - Brochures, 1973-1979 (Box 236, Folder 1714)
    - United States Government Agencies - Alliance for Arts Education - Comprehensive Arts Planning and Development Project - Proposal, May 1974 (Box 236, Folder 1715)
    - United States Government Agencies - Alliance for Arts Education - Comprehensive Arts Planning and Development Project - Converence, October 17-20, 1974 (Box 236, Folder 1716)
    - United States Government Agencies - Alliance for Arts Education - Comprehensive Arts Planning and Development Project - Conference, October 17-20, 1974 (Box 237, Folder 1717)
    - United States Government Agencies - Alliance for Arts Education - Comprehensive Arts Planning and Development Project - Conference, October 17-20, 1974 (Box 237, Folder 1718)
    - United States Government Agencies - Alliance for Arts Education - Comprehensive Arts Planning and Development Project - Planning Arts in Education, October 1974 (Box 237, Folder 1719)
    - United States Government Agencies - Alliance for Arts Education - Correspondence, 1973-1979 (Box 237, Folder 1720)
    - United States Government Agencies - Alliance for Arts Education - Correspondence, 1973-1979 (Box 237, Folder 1721)
    - United States Government Agencies - Alliance for Arts Education - Correspondence, 1973-1979 (Box 237, Folder 1722)
    - United States Government Agencies - Alliance for Arts Education - Directory, 1973 (Box 237, Folder 1723)
    - United States Government Agencies - Alliance for Arts Education - Meetings, 1973-1978 (Box 238, Folder 1724)
    - United States Government Agencies - Alliance for Arts Education - Meetings, 1973-1978 (Box 238, Folder 1725)
    - United States Government Agencies - Alliance for Arts Education - Meetings, 1973-1978 (Box 238, Folder 1726)
    - United States Government Agencies - Alliance for Arts Education - Meetings, 1973-1978 (Box 238, Folder 1727)
    - United States Government Agencies - Alliance for Arts Education - Meetings, 1973-1978 (Box 238, Folder 1728)
    - United States Government Agencies - Alliance for Arts Education - Miscellany, 1975-1977 (Box 238, Folder 1729)
    - United States Government Agencies - American Revolution Bicentennial Committee (ARBC) - Brochures, 1971-1975 (Box 239, Folder 1730)
    - United States Government Agencies - American Revolution Bicentennial Committee (ARBC) - Correspondence, 1971-1973 (Box 239, Folder 1731)
    - United States Government Agencies - American Revolution Bicentennial Committee (ARBC) - Meetings, 1972-1973 (Box 239, Folder 1732)
    - United States Government Agencies - American Revolution Bicentennial Committee (ARBC) - Meetings, 1972-1973 (Box 239, Folder 1733)
    - United States Government Agencies - American Revolution Bicentennial Committee (ARBC) - Meetings, 1972-1973 (Box 239, Folder 1734)
    - United States Government Agencies - American Revolution Bicentennial Committee (ARBC) - Meetings, 1972-1973 (Box 239, Folder 1735)
    - United States Government Agencies - American Revolution Bicentennial Committee (ARBC) - Meetings, 1972-1973 (Box 239, Folder 1736)
    - United States Government Agencies - American Revolution Bicentennial Committee (ARBC) - Meeting, 1973 (Box 240, Folder 1737)
    - United States Government Agencies - American Revolution Bicentennial Committee (ARBC) - Meeting, 1973 (Box 240, Folder 1738)
    - United States Government Agencies - American Revolution Bicentennial Committee (ARBC) - Miscellany, 1972-1973 (Box 240, Folder 1739)
    - United States Government Agencies - American Revolution Bicentennial Committee (ARBC) - Miscellany, 1972-1973 (Box 240, Folder 1740)
    - United States Government Agencies - Department of Health, Education and Welfare (HEW) - Institute of Museum Services, 1972-1973 (Box 240, Folder 1741)
    - United States Government Agencies - Department of Health, Education and Welfare (HEW) - National Institute of Education (NIE) - Brochures, 1970-1975 (Box 240, Folder 1742)
    - United States Government Agencies - Department of Health, Education and Welfare (HEW) - National Institute of Education (NIE) - Correspondence, 1973-1977 (Box 240, Folder 1743)
    - United States Government Agencies - Department of Health, Education and Welfare (HEW) - National Institute of Education (NIE) - Task Force Correspondence, 1973 (Box 241, Folder 1744)
    - United States Government Agencies - Department of Health, Education and Welfare (HEW) - National Institute of Education (NIE) - Meetings, 1973 (Box 241, Folder 1745)
    - United States Government Agencies - Department of Health, Education and Welfare (HEW) - National Institute of Education (NIE) - Meetings, 1973 (Box 241, Folder 1746)
    - United States Government Agencies - Department of Health, Education and Welfare (HEW) - National Institute of Education (NIE) - Miscellany, 1973 (Box 241, Folder 1747)
    - United States Government Agencies - Department of Health, Education and Welfare (HEW) - Office of Child Development - Handbooks, 1970 (Box 241, Folder 1748)
    - United States Government Agencies - Department of Health, Education and Welfare (HEW) - Office of Child Development - Papers, 1975 (Box 241, Folder 1749)
    - United States Government Agencies - Department of Health, Education and Welfare (HEW) - Office of Education (OOE) - Addresses, 1967-1977 (Box 241, Folder 1750)
    - United States Government Agencies - Department of Health, Education and Welfare (HEW) - Office of Education (OOE) - Applications for Grants, 1976-1978 (Box 241, Folder 1751)
    - United States Government Agencies - Department of Health, Education and Welfare (HEW) - Office of Education (OOE) - Arts and Humanities Program, 1969-1973 (Box 242, Folder 1752)
    - United States Government Agencies - Department of Health, Education and Welfare (HEW) - Office of Education (OOE) - Brochures, 1969-1978 (Box 242, Folder 1753)
    - United States Government Agencies - Department of Health, Education and Welfare (HEW) - Office of Education (OOE) - Correspondence, 1968-1979 (Box 242, Folder 1754)
    - United States Government Agencies - Department of Health, Education and Welfare (HEW) - Office of Education (OOE) - Meetings, 1978-1979 (Box 242, Folder 1755)
    - United States Government Agencies - Department of Health, Education and Welfare (HEW) - Office of Education (OOE) - Miscellany, 1968-1974 (Box 242, Folder 1756)
    - United States Government Agencies - Department of Health, Education and Welfare (HEW) - Office of Education (OOE) - Office of Gifted and Talented - Correspondence, 1975 (Box 242, Folder 1757)
    - United States Government Agencies - Department of Health, Education and Welfare (HEW) - Office of Education (OOE) - Office of Gifted and Talented - Meetings, 1975-1978 (Box 242, Folder 1758)
    - United States Government Agencies - Department of Health, Education and Welfare (HEW) - Office of Education (OOE) - Office of Gifted and Talented - Spearfish Conference, October 2-4, 1974 (Box 242, Folder 1759)
    - United States Government Agencies - Federal Council on the Arts and Humanities, 1978-1979 (Box 243, Folder 1760)
    - United States Government Agencies - Institute of American Indian Arts, 1970-1975 (Box 243, Folder 1761)
    - United States Government Agencies - Kennedy Center for the Performing Arts - Brochures, 1974-1979 (Box 243, Folder 1762)
    - United States Government Agencies - Kennedy Center for the Performing Arts - Chairman's National Commission to Expand Black Participation, 1977-1979 (Box 243, Folder 1763)
    - United States Government Agencies - Kennedy Center for the Performing Arts - Correspondence, 1970-1975 (Box 243, Folder 1764)
    - United States Government Agencies - Kennedy Center for the Performing Arts - "Kennedy Center News", 1973-1978 (Box 243, Folder 1765)
    - United States Government Agencies - Kennedy Center for the Performing Arts - National Symphony Advisory Committee, 1977 (Box 243, Folder 1766)
    - United States Government Agencies - National Association for Retired Citizens, 1975 (Box 243, Folder 1767)
    - United States Government Agencies - National Commission of the United Nations Educational, Scientific and Cultural Organization (UNESCO), 1973 (Box 243, Folder 1768)
    - United States Government Agencies - National Conference on Citizenship, 1974 (Box 244, Folder 1769)
    - United States Government Agencies - National Conference on Cultural Resources, 1975 (Box 244, Folder 1770)
    - United States Government Agencies - National Council on the Arts, 1970-1972; 1977 (Box 244, Folder 1771)
    - United States Government Agencies - National Endowment for the Arts (NEA) - Artists-in-Schools Program, 1973-1977 (Box 244, Folder 1772)
    - United States Government Agencies - National Endowment for the Arts (NEA) - Brochures, 1972-1978 (Box 244, Folder 1773)
    - United States Government Agencies - National Endowment for the Arts (NEA) - Correspondence, 1969-1979 (Box 244, Folder 1774)
    - United States Government Agencies - National Endowment for the Arts (NEA) - Correspondence, 1969-1979 (Box 244, Folder 1775)
    - United States Government Agencies - National Endowment for the Arts (NEA) - Guides and Guidelines, 1973-1976 (Box 244, Folder 1776)
    - United States Government Agencies - National Endowment for the Arts (NEA) - Guides and Guidelines, 1977-1979 (Box 245, Folder 1777)
    - United States Government Agencies - National Endowment for the Arts (NEA) - Publications, 1971-1978 (Box 245, Folder 1778)
    - United States Government Agencies - National Endowment for the Arts (NEA) - Publications, 1971-1978 (Box 245, Folder 1779)
    - United States Government Agencies - National Endowment for the Arts (NEA) - Task Force - Correspondence, 1977-1978 (Box 245, Folder 1780)
    - United States Government Agencies - National Endowment for the Arts (NEA) - Task Force - Report (Draft), 1978 (Box 245, Folder 1781)
    - United States Government Agencies - National Endowment for the Arts (NEA) - Task Force - Report (Final), 1978 (Box 245, Folder 1782)
    - United States Government Agencies - National Endowment for the Arts (NEA) - Miscellany, 1971-1978 (Box 246, Folder 1783)
    - United States Government Agencies - National Endowment for the Humanities (NEH) - Brochures, 1969-1976 (Box 246, Folder 1784)
    - United States Government Agencies - National Endowment for the Humanities (NEH) - Correspondence, 1967-1976 (Box 246, Folder 1785)
    - United States Government Agencies - National Endowment for the Humanities (NEH) - Miscellany, 1968-1973 (Box 246, Folder 1786)
    - United States Government Agencies - National Foundation for the Arts and Humanities, 1968-1970; 1979 (Box 246, Folder 1787)
    - United States Government Agencies - National Gallery, 1973-1977 (Box 246, Folder 1788)
    - United States Government Agencies - Office of Economic Opportunity, 1967-1971 (Box 246, Folder 1789)
    - United States Government Agencies - Smithsonian Institution, 1973-1975 (Box 246, Folder 1790)
    - United States Government Agencies - United States Committee for the United Nations International Children's Emergency Fund (UNICEF), 1977-1979 (Box 246, Folder 1791)
    - United States Government Agencies - White House, 1970-1971 (Box 247, Folder 1792)
    - United States Government Agencies - White House Conference on Children, September 1970 (Box 247, Folder 1793)
    - United States Government Agencies - White House Conference on Arts Education, September 8, 1976 (Box 247, Folder 1794)
    - State Agencies - Alabama State Department of Education, 1974 (Box 247, Folder 1795)
    - State Agencies - Arkansas Arts Center, 1973 (Box 247, Folder 1796)
    - State Agencies- Connecticut Commission on the Arts, 1974-1977 (Box 247, Folder 1797)
    - State Agencies - Connecticut Department of Education - Correspondence, 1967-1975 (Box 247, Folder 1798)
    - State Agencies - Connecticut Department of Education - Curriculum Bulletin Series, 1967-1969 (Box 247, Folder 1799)
    - State Agencies - Delaware Arts Council, 1974; 1978 (Box 247, Folder 1800)
    - State Agencies - Idaho State Department of Education, 1974-1975 (Box 247, Folder 1801)
    - State Agencies - Illinois Alliance for Arts Education, 1976 (Box 247, Folder 1802)
    - State Agencies - Illinois Institute for Juvenile Research, 1973 (Box 247, Folder 1803)
    - State Agencies - Illinois Institute for Juvenile Research, 1974-1975 (Box 248, Folder 1804)
    - State Agencies - Illinois State Board of Education, 1975-1978 (Box 248, Folder 1805)
    - State Agencies - Iowa Arts Council, 1975-1978 (Box 248, Folder 1806)
    - State Agencies - Iowa Department of Public Instruction, 1976-1978 (Box 248, Folder 1807)
    - State Agencies - Louisiana Alliance for Arts Education, 1975 (Box 248, Folder 1808)
    - State Agencies - Louisiana Council for Music and Performing Arts, 1971 (Box 248, Folder 1809)
    - State Agencies - Maryland State Department of Education, 1976-1977 (Box 248, Folder 1810)
    - State Agencies - Minnesota Alliance for Arts in Education, 1974-1975 (Box 248, Folder 1811)
    - State Agencies - Minnesota - Correspondence, 1975-1976 (Box 248, Folder 1812)
    - State Agencies - Minnesota Department of Education, 1976 (Box 248, Folder 1813)
    - State Agencies - Minnesota - Governor's Commission on the Arts, 1977 (Box 249, Folder 1814)
    - State Agencies - Minnesota State Arts Council, 1969-1977 (Box 249, Folder 1815)
    - State Agencies - Montana State Department of Public Instruction - Correspondence, 1968; 1975-1977 (Box 249, Folder 1816)
    - State Agencies - Montana State Department of Public Instruction - Visit, November 3-5, 1975 (Box 249, Folder 1817)
    - State Agencies - Nebraska Alliance for Education, 1978 (Box 249, Folder 1818)
    - State Agencies - Nebraska State Arts Council, 1975-1977 (Box 249, Folder 1819)
    - State Agencies - New Hampshire Department of Education, 1976-1977 (Box 249, Folder 1820)
    - State Agencies - New Jersey Alliance for Arts Education, 1975 (Box 249, Folder 1821)
    - State Agencies - New Jersey - Correspondence, 1977 (Box 249, Folder 1822)
    - State Agencies - New Jersey Department of Education, 1975-1977 (Box 250, Folder 1823)
    - State Agencies - New Jersey Department of Education - Publications, 1977 (Box 250, Folder 1824)
    - State Agencies - New Jersey State Council on the Arts, 1973-1978 (Box 250, Folder 1825)
    - State Agencies - New Mexico - Alliance for Arts Education, 1975 (Box 250, Folder 1826)
    - State Agencies - North Carolina Arts Council, 1972-1977 (Box 250, Folder 1827)
    - State Agencies - North Carolina Department of Public Instruction, 1974-1977 (Box 250, Folder 1828)
    - State Agencies - Ohio Art Education Association, 1973-1974 (Box 250, Folder 1829)
    - State Agencies - Ohio Department of Education, 1970; 1974-1978 (Box 250, Folder 1830)
    - State Agencies - Oregon - Miscellany, 1968-1977 (Box 251, Folder 1831)
    - State Agencies - Rhode Island State Council of the Arts - Brochures, 1972; 1978 (Box 251, Folder 1832)
    - State Agencies - Rhode Island State Council of the Arts - Correspondence, 1971-1979 (Box 251, Folder 1833)
    - State Agencies - Rhode Island State Council of the Arts - Meetings, 1968; 1972 (Box 251, Folder 1834)
    - State Agencies - Rhode Island State Council of the Arts - Reports, 1970-1972 (Box 251, Folder 1835)